{"data":[{"question":"We decided not to go on a picnic because it was raining ___.","a":"hardly","b":"badly","c":"heavily","d":"strongly","answer":"3","explain":"\n- We use heavily (adverb) after rain (verb) to imply that rain falls hard ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Wait till you are more ___. It's better to be sure than sorry.","a":"certain","b":"inspired","c":"satisfied","d":"calm","answer":"1","explain":".\n- Certain:confident and sure, without any doubts","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"I haven't been to New Zealand yet. \"I haven't been there, ___\"","a":"also","b":"too","c":"neither","d":"either","answer":"2","explain":".\n- Too: used at the end of a sentence or clause to mean 'also'","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"The lawn are watered ___.","a":"every other day","b":"each other day","c":"every of two days","d":"each of the days","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Every other: the first, third, fifth etc or the second, fourth, sixth ect","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"As soon as he entered the room, Mr. Li took ___ his coat and cap and sat down.","a":"out","b":"off","c":"down","d":"away","answer":"2","explain":". \n- Take off: to remove a piece of clothing\u00a0","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"The students are ___ teenagers between the ages of fifteen and eighteen.","a":"almost","b":"most","c":"at most","d":"mostly","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Mostly (adv): used to talk about most members of a group, most occasions, most parts of something etc [= mainly]","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Excuse me, is this Dr. Brown's office? \"I'm sorry, but Dr. Brown _________ works here. He left about two weeks ago.\"","a":"no more","b":"not now","c":"no longer","d":"not still","answer":"3","explain":"\n- No longer\/not any longer: used when something used to happen or be true in the past but does not happen or is not true now","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"It was incredible that so ___ workers should do so ___ work in a single day in ancient times.","a":"few, many","b":"few, much","c":"little, many","d":"little, much","answer":"2","explain":".\n- Few, many + countable noun\n- Little, much + uncountable noun","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Mom, I think I'd better stay at home for another day or two. \"Not really, my dear. You're ___ to go back to school.\"","a":"so good","b":"so well","c":"good enough","d":"well enough","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Adj + enough to do sth \n+ Well (adj): healthy","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Can you believe that in ___ a rich country there should be ___ many poor people?","a":"such, so","b":"such, such","c":"so, such","d":"so, so","answer":"1","explain":".\n- Such + (a) noun phrase\n- So many + countable noun","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"}]}